Eng

- WORD A DAY (7 Mins)

   - Learn from http://www.learnersdictionary.com/word-of-the-day 
   - Info Mapping with Word, Sentences, Synonyms, and different forms of the word.


- IDIOM A DAY (5 Mins)

   - Learn from https://idioms.thefreedictionary.com/, http://www.englishdaily626.com/idioms.php, https://www.phrasemix.com/examples
   - Learn a sentence with this phrase
   - Answer if - Does your native language use a similar phrase? When might you use the phrase?
   - Come up with your own sentence using the idiom in a way that you would in your everyday life.
  
  
- Strengthen Your Grammar Skills (5 Mins)

   - Learn from http://www.5minuteenglish.com/grammar.htm, http://www.chompchomp.com/terms.htm     https://learnenglish.britishcouncil.org/grammar/intermediate-to-upper-intermediate  
   - Read a short grammar lesson
   - Visit any website, http://www.elle.com/beauty/health-fitness/advice/a27/i-got-in-shape-in-two-weeks/?mag=elm&click=yr
   - Look for examples of the grammar rule being used on the website. For example, if you’re learning about conditionals, you can search the page for the word “if” (just press Ctrl+F and enter the words you’re looking for).
   - Create your own example with the rule. 
   
- Read the News (13 Mins)

   - Examples - http://learningenglish.voanews.com/, http://www.breakingnewsenglish.com/, http://www.newsinlevels.com/
   - Find a news article that interests you.
   - Scan the article for words you don’t know and find their definition. That means you should look through the article without actually reading every word.
   - Read the article.
   - Did you understand at least the basic idea of the article? Explain out loud what the article was about, as if you’re talking to someone about it.
   
   
- 5 Minute Review Exercise 

   - When you do this exercise, do everything out loud to practice speaking. Write everything down on paper to practice writing. You can also quietly review it all in your head.
   - Use your new vocabulary word in a sentence.
   - Use your new phrase in a sentence.
   - Use the grammar rule you learned in a sentence.
   - Summarize the article you read in a sentence or two.  

----------------------------------------------------

RN updates

update the short links in the last few RN items

Check with Sherlene/George for Logo 
  https://expensesreceipt.com/gas-fuel.html

Western Overseas
UCan
Canam
9000096753 - 17700   


Other work

https://learndigital.withgoogle.com/digitalunlocked/course/digital-marketing
https://knowledgeenthusiast.com/2021/05/02/15-best-digital-marketing-certifications/
https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/certifications/data-analyst-associate/
https://www.simplilearn.com/business-analyst-certification-training-course#what-business-analysis-areas-are-covered-in-the-babok-guide

https://gpslearning.deloitte.com/SitePages/index.aspx#/home

German

Apply for any Masters course
learn German @ https://www.goethe.de/en/spr/kup/prf/prf/sd1/ueb.html 
Give A1 test and pass
Apply for either Study/ Working Visa



